dealersocket.com 2019-05-25

# DealerSocket Privacy Policy

Last Updated: May 2019

At DealerSocket, we recognize that privacy is important to our customers, so we design and operate our services with the protection of your personal information in mind. This Privacy Policy applies to DealerSocket and our and subsidiaries (“DealerSocket”) and outlines the types of personal information we collect when you use DealerSocket’s website, emails, apps, and visit us at tradeshows or events (collectively, the “services”) or when you contact us in any manner. It also describes how we use your personal information, and some of the steps we take to safeguard it.

### Data Collection

The personal information we collect depends on how you interact with us, the services you use, and the choices you make. 

Information you provide directly: Some of our services require you to register for an account. DealerSocket asks you for some personal information in order to create an account (typically your name, email address and a password for your account). For certain services, we may request credit card or other payment information. When you contact us for demos or information about our services, we may also collect information about your job (such as your position or title), company or industry, the state or country where you reside, and a phone number.

Information collected automatically: As further described in the Cookies and Similar Technologies section below, when you use our services, some information is collected automatically. For example, when you visit our websites, our web servers automatically log your computer’s operating system, Internet Protocol address, access times, browser type and language, the website you visited before our site, and your activity on our websites.

### Data Use

DealerSocket uses personal information collected through our services for purposes described in this privacy policy or otherwise disclosed to you. For example, we use personal information to:

  * provide and deliver our services, including securing, troubleshooting, improving, and personalizing those services;
  * operate our business, such as improving our internal operations, securing our systems, and detecting fraudulent or illegal activity;
  * understand you and your preferences to enhance your experience and enjoyment using our services;
  * provide customer support and respond to your questions;
  * send you information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages;
  * communicate with you about new services, offers, promotions, rewards, contests, upcoming events, and other about our services and those of our selected partners (see the Your Privacy Choices/Opt-Out section of this privacy policy for how to change your preferences for marketing emails); and
  * display advertising to you (see the Cookies section of this privacy policy for information about your advertising choices)

In carrying out these purposes, we combine data we collect from different sources to give you a more seamless, consistent, and personalized experience.

### Cookies and Similar Technologies

DealerSocket uses cookies, pixels, and similar technologies to operate our websites and online services. Cookies are small text files placed on your device that can be read by a web server that placed the cookie. We use cookies to remember your preferences and settings, enable you to sign-in, provide interest-based advertising, improve the quality of our services and to better understand how people interact with us. DealerSocket does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people search. 

Our websites may include web beacons and cookies from third-party service providers. In some cases, that is because we have hired the third party to provide services on our behalf, such as site analytics. Because your browser connects to those third parties' web servers to retrieve that content, those third parties are able to set or read their own cookies on your device and may collect information about your online activities across websites or online services.

Many of the third-party providers them are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA), which each provide a simple way to opt out of ad targeting from participating companies, which you can access at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.aspx and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/.

Most browsers have controls that limit how websites can use cookies. Instructions for blocking or deleting cookies may be available in each browser's privacy or help documentation. Please be aware that if you choose to block cookies, certain website features that depend on cookies may no longer function. If you choose to delete cookies, settings and preferences controlled by those cookies, including advertising preferences, may be deleted and may need to be recreated.

### Information Sharing and Transfers

We share personal information with your consent or for the following purposes:

We provide such information to subsidiaries and to trusted businesses or persons working on our behalf.

If you have an account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent. We may also disclose and transfer personal information in connection with or preparation for a corporate transaction, such as a merger, transfer, divestiture, or sale of all or a portion of our business or assets.We will transfer, disclose, and preserve personal information when we believe that doing so is necessary to:

  * Comply with applicable law or respond to valid legal process, including from law enforcement or other government agencies;
  * Protect our customers and others, for example to prevent spam or attempts to defraud users of our services, or to help prevent the loss of life or serious injury of anyone;
  * Operate and maintain the security of our products, including prevent or stop an attack on our computer systems or networks; or
  * Protect our rights or property, including enforcing the terms of our agreements.

We may store and process personal information collected on our site in the United States or any other country in which DealerSocket Inc., or its agents maintain facilities. While such information is outside of your country of residence, it is subject to laws of such other countries, and may be subject to disclosure to the governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies of such other country, pursuant to the laws of such country.

Please note that some of our services may include references or links to products or services provided by third parties whose privacy practices differ from ours. If you provide personal information to any of those third parties, or consent to our sharing personal information with them, that data is governed by their privacy statements.

We may share aggregated, anonymized information with business partners, advertisers, and others.

### Information Security

We take reasonable and appropriate steps to protect personal information against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. 

### Your Privacy Choices - Opt-out

Marketing: DealerSocket provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving marketing email messages from us or change preferences via a link in the footer of our marketing email messages. Alternatively, you may email us at [info@dealersocket.com.](mailto:info@dealersocket.com)

Online Advertising: To learn some of the ways that you can opt-out of targeted online advertising, see the section above titled “Cookies and Similar Technologies" for more information. Please note that DealerSocket does not have access to or direct control over cookies or other technologies these third parties may use to collect information about your interests, and the information practices are not covered by this privacy policy. Some of these companies offer an opt out of online and mobile ad targeting. To learn more, please visit the [Network Advertising Initiative](https://www.networkadvertising.org/) or [Digital Advertising Alliance.](https://digitaladvertisingalliance.org/) In Canada, please visit [Digital Advertising Alliance Canada.](https://youradchoices.ca/)

**Do Not Track.** Some browsers have incorporated "Do Not Track" (DNT) features that can send a signal to the websites you visit indicating you do not wish to be tracked. Because there is not a common understanding of how to interpret the DNT signal, our websites do not currently respond to browser DNT signals. Instead, you can use the range of other tools to control data collection and use, including the cookie controls and advertising controls described above.

### Changes to this Policy

We will update this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect changes in our services, how we use personal information, or the applicable law. We will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are material, we will also provide notice or obtain consent regarding such changes as may be required by law. Each version will be noted at the top of the page.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any additional questions, please feel free to contact us any time at:

DealerSocket Inc.  
7301 State Hwy 161  
Irving, TX 75039
